futurelooks.com 2008-07-23

# Futurelooks :: Digital Lifestyle and Technology for the Masses

**Futurelooks** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information for audience analysis.

We recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of you as a user of this Website. This Website does not collect Personal Information about you except for information that you voluntarily provide (for example, when you submit an email to us with comments about our web site or products reviewed on the web site or provide answers to a voluntary readership survey.)

We consider the following to be Personal Information: Your name, address, phone number, date of birth, job, personal interests, credit card information, your e-mail address.

This site contains links to other sites. Futurelooks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies except in the case of our photogallery and forum where passwords are required to acces custom profiles.

Futurelooks sometime works with third parties that serve ads to this site. These parties have their own privacy policy. These third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our website.

**Public Forums**

This site makes use of forums and/or message boards available to its users. These are located at [this link](http://www.futurelooks.com/forums). Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However in the event of a security breach of this site please note that no personal information of the visitors would be accessible online as none are stored locally.

**Supplementation of Information**

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

**Correct/Update**

Information volunteered by you for the purpose of using our [message boards](http://www.futurelooks.com/forums) or [photogallery](http://www.futurelooks.com/photopost) can be corrected at anytime by the user via their account profile.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can use our [Contact Form](http://www.futurelooks.com/contact/)
